Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York (ACUSNY); Records apap003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Membership Files, 1943; 1949-1991; 6; 1.33 cubic ft.
  - St. John Fisher College, 1955 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 84)
  - St. John's University, 1961 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 85)
  - St. Thomas Aquinas, 1960 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 86)
  - Stenotype Institute, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 87)
  - SUC Brockport, 1943 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 88)
  - SUC Cortland, 1943 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 89)
  - SUC Fredonia, 1943 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 90)
  - SUC Plattsburgh, 1943 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 91)
  - SUC Potsdam, 1943 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 92)
  - Suffolk County Community College, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 93)
  - Teachers College: Columbia University, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 94)
  - The King's College, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 95)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1971-1974 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 96)
  - Utica College of Syracuse University, 1965-1972 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 97)
  - Utica School of Commerce, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 98)
  - Villa Maria College of Buffalo, 1964-1971 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 99)
  - Wells College, 1969-1975 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 100)
  - Westchester Business Institute, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 101)
  - Wood School, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 102)
  - Yeshiva University, 1965 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 103)
  - York College, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 104)
  - Membership List, 1980-1991 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files), Folder 1)
  - Publications, 1980-1984; 1988-1992 (Box 2 (6-Membership Files), Folder 2)
- Publications, 1941; 1980-1984; 1988-1992; 7; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Contains "The Education of a Teacher," "Introduction to ACUSNY", Newsletters 1980-1984, "News from ACUSNY" 1988-1992, "Communiversity" 1991.
  - "The Education of a Teacher" (pamphlet), [1941] (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
  - "Introduction to ACUSNY" (pamphlet), ca. 1989 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
  - "Newsletter", 1980-1984 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
  - "News from ACUSNY", 1988-1992 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
  - "Communiversity", 1991 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
    Joint publication of ACUSNY and the Governor's Office for Voluntary Services.
- Minute Books, 1948-1991; 8; 0.4 cubic ft.
  The series consists of eighteen volumes of minute books, covering the years 1948-1991. Included are minutes of special meetings, such as annual meetings and ACUSNY Executive Committee meetings, lists of participants, legislation reports, financial reports, general correspondence, in particular from the executive vice president, newsletters, campus guides of different universities, reports on special project, especially the Minority Faculty Project (vol. XVII) and reports on programs, such as "Problems and Prospects of Higher Education in the Next Two Decades"(vol. XII). Volume eighteen contains an index which covers books I-XVIII.
  - Minute Book I, 1948 September-1955 May (Box 1 (8-Minute Books), Folder 1)
  - Minute Book II, 1955 September-1960 December (Box 1 (8-Minute Books), Folder 2)
  - Minute Book III, 1961 January-1964 May (Box 1 (8-Minute Books), Folder 3)
  - Minute Book IV, 1964 June-1966 August (Box 1 (8-Minute Books), Folder 4)
  - Minute Book V, 1966 September-1968 July (Box 1 (8-Minute Books), Folder 5)
  - Minute Book VI, 1968 August-1970 July (Box 1 (8-Minute Books), Folder 6)
  - Minute Book VII, 1970 July-1972 June (Box 1 (8-Minute Books), Folder 7)
  - Minute Book VIII, 1972 July-1973 December (Box 1 (8-Minute Books), Folder 8)
  - Minute Book IX, 1974 January-1975 June (Box 1 (8-Minute Books), Folder 9)
  - Minute Book X, 1975 June-1977 June (Box 2 (8-Minute Books), Folder 1)
  - Minute Book XI, 1977 July-1979 October (Box 2 (8-Minute Books), Folder 2)
  - Minute Book XII, 1979 November-1981 June (Box 2 (8-Minute Books), Folder 3)
  - Minute Book XIII, 1981 August 20-1983 April 11 (Box 2 (8-Minute Books), Folder 4)
  - Minute Book XIV, 1983 May-1985 October 18 (Box 2 (8-Minute Books), Folder 5)
  - Minute Book XV, 1986 January 31-1988 November 5 (Box 2 (8-Minute Books), Folder 6)
  - Minute Book XVI, 1988 November 5-1989 November 4 (Box 2 (8-Minute Books), Folder 7)
  - Minute Book XVII, 1989 November 4-1991 June 28 (Box 2 (8-Minute Books), Folder 8)
  - Minute Book XVIII, 1991 June 28-1991 June 30 (Box 2 (8-Minute Books), Folder 9)
    (Includes index to book I-XVIII).
- Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1985-1992; 9; 1.33 cubic ft.
  Contains meeting minutes, membership lists of the Board of Trustees, bylaws of ACUSNY, financial reports, and background information on economical impacts of SUNY Community Colleges and CUNY. The series also contains correspondence with the ACUSNY Executive Director, members of CUNY and the ACUSNY Steering Committee, as well as university and college presidents. Prominent topics include the Visiting Student Program, 11/2/1989; a report on the Minority Faculty Project, designation of Presidents Committee, discussion of funding, 12/13/1990; the ACUSNY retirement plan, 12/13/1990; the discussion of Higher Education and the Economy of the State, 1992; Adoption of a resolution regarding the Einstein/Schweitzer Chairs, 1992; and the discussion of federal issues affecting higher education, 1992.
  - Meeting, 1985 February 26 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 1)
  - Meeting, 1986 February 26 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 2)
  - Meeting, 1987 March 20 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 3)
  - Meeting, 1988 March 2 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 4)
  - Meeting, 1988 November 3 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 5)
  - Meeting, 1989 March 2 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 6)
  - Meeting, 1989 June 27-1989 June 28 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 7)
  - Meeting, 1989 November 2 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 1990 March 9 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 9)
  - Meeting, 1990 June 11 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 10)
  - Mail Ballot, 1990 December 13 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 11)
  - Meeting, 1991 February 5 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 12)
  - Meeting, 1991 June 28 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 13)
  - Meeting, 1991 November 12 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 14)
  - Meeting, 1992 March 5 (Box 1 (9-Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes), Folder 15)
- Minority Faculty Project, 1988-1990; 10; 4 cubic ft.
  The series illustrates the mission and goals of the Minority Faculty Project, the efforts done to promote minority students, and provides detailed information on its different activities. It also contains correspondence with the ACUSNY Executive Director, presidents of the Minority Faculty Project and presidents of funds and councils for financial aid. The series also documents meetings and minority programs of individual universities of New York State and of other states of the U.S. It covers the time period between 1988 and 1990.
  - Activities Outline, Overview and Notes, 1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 1)
  - Activity 1- Early Identification and Name Exchange, 1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 2)
  - Activity 3- Graduate School Recruitment Forms, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 3)
  - Activity 4- Clearing House on Summer Research Apprenticeships, 1988 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 4)
  - Activity 5- Annual Conference Graduate Students, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 5)
  - CUNY (City University of New York), 1988-1989 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Corporation- Proposal and Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 7)
  - Central New York Forum Minority Faculty Project, 1988-1991 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 8)
  - Columbia University, 1988 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 9)
  - Cornell University, 1986-1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1990 June-1992 March (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1990 January-1990 June (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1989 April-1989 December (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1988 September-1989 April (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 14)
  - Data, Undated (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 15)
  - Federal Government, 1988 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 16)
  - FIPSE (Fund for the improvement of postsecondary education), 1990-1991 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 17)
  - Minority Faculty: Funding, 1988-1991 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 18)
  - GRE/College Board Minority Faculty Project, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 19)
  - Minority Faculty: Project Host Institutions, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 20)
  - Lubin House Meeting, 1988 September 27 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 21)
  - Minority Participation, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 22)
  - National Name Exchange, 1988 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 23)
  - New York State Forum on Graduate Education for Minorities, 1992 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 24)
  - National Science Foundation, 1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 25)
  - New York State Legislation, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 26)
  - Notes- Miscellaneous, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 27)
  - Presidents Committee, 1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 28)
  - Prospectus, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 29)
  - Regional Meeting, Albany, 1989 November 9 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 30)
  - Regional Meeting, New York City, 1989 November 8 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 31)
  - Regional Meeting, Rochester, 1989 November 10 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 32)
  - Responses and Survey, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 33)
  - Research Scholar Program for Minority Students, 1987 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 34)
  - SUNY, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 35)
  - SUNY at Stony Brook, 1988-1992 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 36)
  - States: Florida/McKnight Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 37)
  - States: New Jersey, 1988 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 38)
  - Minority Faculty Project Steering Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 39)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 40)
  - Westchester Colleges Racial Diversity Project, 1990 (Box 1 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 41)
  - Activity 8 - Annual Directory of PHD Candidates and Recipients, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 1)
  - #8 - Correspondence & Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 2)
  - #8 - Institutional Representatives, 1991 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 3)
  - Directory: Keyed no Questions, 1991 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 4)
  - Directory Label Problems, 1991 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 5)
  - Directory: Not Used, 1991 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 6)
  - Directory Survey of Candidates, 1992 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 7)
  - Minority Faculty Project, Undated; 2 binders (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project))
  - Minority Faculty Project: Directory of Minority PhD's + ABD's, 1991 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 8)
  - Minority Faculty Project Institutional Survey Responses, 1989; 3 folders (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 9-11)
  - Minority Faculty Project Planning Grant - President's Response, 1989 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 12)
  - Minority Faculty Project Planning Grant - Survey Responses, 1989 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 13)
  - Minority Faculty Project Responses, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (10-Minority Faculty Project), Folder 14)
- Service Files, 1988-1992; 11; 2.66 cubic ft.
  The series illustrates ACUSNY's involvement in service projects between 1989 and 1992, which encourage community service activities by college students in New York State. It also documents the exchange of information about college service programs and the views of the higher education community on public policy issues related to student community service. Included are newsletters, newspaper articles, background information on various service and volunteer programs, documents on the campus compact, Dec.'88-March '90., and correspondence, especially to the governor's office for voluntary service and various student service program committees.
  - Governor's Office of Voluntary Service, 1989-1992 (Box 1 (11-Service Files), Folder 1)
  - Legislative SUB Committee for Service, 1990 (Box 1 (11-Service Files), Folder 2)
  - National Community Service Act, 1990 (Box 1 (11-Service Files), Folder 3)
  - Service Correspondence, 1990 March 9 (Box 1 (11-Service Files), Folder 4)
  - Service/Campus Compact, 1988 December-1989 October (Box 1 (11-Service Files), Folder 5)
  - Service/Campus Compact, 1989 November 2-1990 March 9 (Box 1 (11-Service Files), Folder 6)
  - Service - Information, Request & Response, Undated (Box 2 (11-Service Files), Folder 1)
  - Service: Interagency Student Volunteer Service Committee, 1991 (Box 2 (11-Service Files), Folder 2)
  - Service: Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (11-Service Files), Folder 3)
  - Service Project: Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (11-Service Files), Folder 4)
  - Service: Responsible Service Subcommittee, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (11-Service Files), Folder 5)
  - Service: State Legislation, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (11-Service Files), Folder 6)
  - SUNY: Volunteerism & Community Service, 1989 (Box 2 (11-Service Files), Folder 7)
- Visiting Student Program, 1969-1990; 12; 1.33 cubic ft.
  The series illustrates ACUSNY's engagement in the Visiting Student Program which allows students enrolled at a participating college to visit another institution in New York State for up to a year without formal transfer. Contains background information on the program, receipts, lists of participating institutions, responses to a survey, 1988, the original Visiting Student Program Handbook, incoming and outgoing reports, 1990, and correspondence, 1969-1990, in particular to participating institutions and the Visiting Student Program Advisory Panel. Prominent topics include the improvement of publicity of the Visiting Student Program, 1969; solidarity in the higher education community, 1980; international programming, 1989. 0.
  - Correspondence, 1966-1990 (Box 1 (12-Visiting Student Program), Folder 1)
  - Forms, Undated (Box 1 (12-Visiting Student Program), Folder 2)
  - Receipts, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (12-Visiting Student Program), Folder 3)
  - Responses to Survey, 1988 (Box 1 (12-Visiting Student Program), Folder 4)
  - VSP - Handbook Originals, Undated (Box 1 (12-Visiting Student Program), Folder 5)
  - VSP - Incoming and Outgoing Reports ACUSNY, 1990 (Box 1 (12-Visiting Student Program), Folder 6)
  - Accounting Files, 1973; 1975-1992 (Box 1 (12-Visiting Student Program), Folder 7)
- Accounting Files, 1973; 1975-1992; 13; 10 cubic ft.
  Contains accounting files of the fiscal years from 1984-1991, cash receipt and entry journals, bills paid, tax records, especially Federal and New York State Income Tax remittance copies, 1984, accounting files of Annual Meetings, 1990-1992, and the Minority Faculty Project, IRS-original tax exempt information, 1973, registration statements of the employee benefit plan, 1975-1990, and miscellaneous things, such as accounting files of office furniture, insurance, New York Telephone, and Albany parking.
  - Accounts Receivable, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 1)
  - ACE Accounting File, 1991 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 2)
  - Albany Parking, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 4)
  - Bitnet Contract - SUNYA, 1989 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 5)
  - Budget - ACUSNY, 1991 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 6)
  - Cancelled Checks, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 7)
  - CICU (Hospital Insurance), 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 8)
  - Check Register, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 9)
  - Central Business Equipment, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 10)
  - Complete List of Office Furniture, 1985-1990 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 11)
  - Dreyfus Liquid Assets, 1991 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 12)
  - Dues Received, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 13)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 14)
  - Insurance Package Liability, 1989-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 15)
  - Insurance - Workers Compensation, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 16)
  - IRS - Original Tax Exempt Information, 1973 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 17)
  - MFP Checking, 1991 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 18)
  - MICO, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous MFP, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 21)
  - NLS Printing, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 22)
  - NYS Income Tax, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 23)
  - NYS Unemployment Insurance, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 24)
  - Newkirk Products, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 25)
  - New York Telephone, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 26)
  - Payroll, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 27)
  - Pitney Bowes, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 28)
  - Purchase Orders, 1991; 4 folders (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 29-32)
  - RCI, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 33)
  - Sales Tax Exemptions, City, County, State, 1949; 1965; 1970-1971 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 34)
  - SUNY Invoice, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 35)
  - Service, 1991 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 36)
  - Sussman, George (Accounting File), 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 37)
  - TIAA/CREF - Checks, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 38)
  - TIAA/CREF - Miscellaneous, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 39)
  - Tax Exempt Reports, 1980- (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 40)
  - Tax Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 41)
  - Tax, 1975-1990 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 42)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 43)
  - Treasurer's File, 1966-1968; 1980-1989 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 44)
  - United States Post Office, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 45)
  - United Parcel Service, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 46)
  - Urbach, Kahn & Werlin, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 47)
  - Void Checks, 1991 (Box 1 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 48)
  - Accounting Files, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 1)
  - Accounting Files, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 2)
  - Accounting Files, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 3)
  - ACUSNY - Bills Paid, 07/01/1984-12/31/1984 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 4)
  - ACUSNY - Bills Paid, 01/01/1985-06/30/1985 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 5)
  - ACUSNY - W4 Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 6)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York - Financial Reports, 1985; 1987-1990; 4 binders (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files))
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York - Letter of Recommendations to Management, 1988 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 7)
  - Cash Receipts and Entry Journal, 07/01/1985-06/30/1986 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 8)
  - Cash Receipts and Entry Journal, 07/01/1986-06/30/1987 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 9)
  - Checks processed, 1984-1991 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 10)
  - Federal NYS Income Tax Remittance Copies, 1984 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 11)
  - Payroll & Tax Records, 1985 (Box 2 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 12)
  - Accounting Files, 1987-1989 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 1)
  - Accounting Files, Fiscal, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 2)
  - Accounting Files, Fiscal, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 3)
  - Accounts Payable, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 4)
  - Accounts Payable, 1987-1989 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 5)
  - Dreyfus Liquid Assets, 1989 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 6)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1988 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 7)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 8)
  - Insurance (Alexander & Alexander) D20537875, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 9)
  - Insurance (The Hartford), 1988-1989 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 10)
  - New York State Income Tax, 1988 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 11)
  - NYS Income Tax, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 12)
  - NYS Unemployment Insurance, 1990 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 13)
  - NYS Unemployment Insurance, NYS Wage Report, 1988 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 14)
  - Payroll, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 15)
  - Tax Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 16)
  - Accounting Files, Fiscal, 1990-1991 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 1)
  - ACUSNY Annual Meeting, 11/08/1990-11/09/1990 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 2)
  - Cash Receipts and Entry Journal, 07/01/1988-06/30/1989 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 3)
  - Cash Receipts and Entry Journal, 07/01/1987-06/30/1988 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 4)
  - ACUSNY Membership Dues, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 5)
  - Dues, 1985 July-1986 June (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 6)
  - Dues, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 7)
  - Dues, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 8)
  - Dues, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 9)
  - Dues, 1989-1990 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 10)
  - Dues - Receipts, Undated (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 11)
  - MFP Checking, 1990-1991 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 12)
  - MFP Checking Account, 1989-1990 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 13)
  - MFP Elisabeth Wadsworth Expenses, 1989-1990 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 14)
  - MFP Finances, 1989-1990 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 15)
  - MFP Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 16)
  - Payroll, 1990 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 17)
  - Registrations Presidents Meeting, 02/05/1990 (Box 4 (13-Accounting Files), Folder 18)
  - The Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of NY - Financial Reports, 1974-1982; 1988-1991; 4 binders (Box 5 (13-Accounting Files))